Kheel Center AV Collection 6118 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- There's a Whole Lot More of Us Than They Think - Anne Feeney and Friends - #233 (Box 345)
  - There's a Whole Lot More of Us Than They Think - Anne Feeney and Friends (Box 345)
    #233
- If I can't dance it's not my revolution - Anne Feeney - #234 (Box 346)
  - If I can't dance it's not my revolution - Anne Feeney (Box 346)
    #234
- Don't Mourn - Organize - by Joe Hill - #235 (Box 347)
  - Don't Mourn - Organize - by Joe Hill (Box 347)
    #235
- Homemade by Harry Stamper - #236 (Box 348)
  - Homemade by Harry Stamper (Box 348)
    #236
- Here's to you Harry! - Harry Stamper and the Blastido Band - #237 (Box 349)
  - Here's to you Harry! - Harry Stamper and the Blastido Band (Box 349)
    #237
- We Are The Working Class by Eddie Starr - #238 (Box 350)
  - We Are The Working Class by Eddie Starr (Box 350)
    #238
- Not Bread Alone - #239 (2 copies) (Box 351)
  - Not Bread Alone (Box 351)
    #239 (2 copies)
- Ossie & Ruby and Bread & Roses - #240 (Box 352)
  - Ossie & Ruby and Bread & Roses (Box 352)
    #240
- Movimiento Music - #249 (Box 353)
  - Movimiento Music (Box 353)
    #249
- Wisconsin Ideas Network - #250 (Box 354)
  - Wisconsin Ideas Network (Box 354)
    #250
- McClellan Committee & Teamsters Expulsion #5 - #251 (Box 355)
  - McClellan Committee & Teamsters Expulsion #5 (Box 355)
    #251
- Labor and the War Effort #7 - #252 (Box 356)
  - Labor and the War Effort #7 (Box 356)
    #252
- Labor and Foreign Policy #8 - #253 (Box 357)
  - Labor and Foreign Policy #8 (Box 357)
    #253
- Labor and Communism #3 - 1949 CIO Convention - #254 (Box 358)
  - Labor and Communism #3 - 1949 CIO Convention (Box 358)
    #254
- New York City Labor Chorus - Cooper Union - Great Hall, June 11, 1995 - #257 (Box 359)
  - New York City Labor Chorus - Cooper Union - Great Hall, June 11, 1995 (Box 359)
    #257
- The Jewish Immigrant Experience in America by Joe Glazer - #261 (Box 360)
  - The Jewish Immigrant Experience in America by Joe Glazer (Box 360)
    #261
- Songs of the Jewish Worker by Frank Krasnowsky - #262 (Box 361)
  - Songs of the Jewish Worker by Frank Krasnowsky (Box 361)
    #262
- Working My Life Away - #263 (Box 362)
  - Working My Life Away (Box 362)
    #263
- Working Women's Songs by Pat Wynne - #264 (Box 363)
  - Working Women's Songs by Pat Wynne (Box 363)
    #264
- War Zone, Union Jax - #265 (Box 364)
  - War Zone, Union Jax (Box 364)
    #265
- Look to the Left by Anne Feeney - #266 (2 copies) (Box 365)
  - Look to the Left by Anne Feeney - (Box 365)
    #266 (2 copies)
- Utah Phillips - #267 (Box 366.1)
  - Utah Phillips - (Box 366)
    #267 (2 copies)
- Utah Phillips - #267 (Box 366.2)
- Bread and Raises by Bobbie McGee - #268 (Box 367)
  - Bread and Raises by Bobbie McGee - (Box 367)
    #268
- Songs of the Working People - #269 (Box 368.1)
  - Songs of the Working People - (Box 368)
    #269 (2 copies)
- Songs of the Working People - #269 (Box 368.2)
- Labor Songs by Joe Glazer - #270 (Box 369)
  - Labor Songs by Joe Glazer - (Box 369)
    #270
- Working Class Reminiscing and Visions by Mike Stout - #271 (Box 370)
  - Working Class Reminiscing and Visions by Mike Stout - (Box 370)
    #271
- Secora - Gospel/Labor Music: The tie that binds - #272 (Box 371)
  - Secora - Gospel/Labor Music: The tie that binds - (Box 371)
    #272
- New York City Labor Chorus - #273 (Box 372)
  - New York City Labor Chorus - (Box 372)
    #273
- The Bones of Contention- #275 (Box 373)
  - The Bones of Contention- (Box 373)
    #275
- Bev Grant: We Were There! - #278 (2 copies) (Box 374)
  - Bev Grant: We Were There! - (Box 374)
    #278 (2 copies)
- Celebrating the IAM: 1888-1988 - A Proud century of union songs by Derek Morgan and friends - #279 (Box 375)
  - Celebrating the IAM: 1888-1988 - A Proud century of union songs by Derek Morgan and friends - (Box 375)
    #279
- Working Verses Dialeclectics - #280 (Box 376)
  - Working Verses Dialeclectics - (Box 376)
    #280
- Out of Darkness by Tom Juravich - #281 (Box 377)
  - Out of Darkness by Tom Juravich - (Box 377)
    #281
- They'll Never Keep Us Down - #282 (Box 378)
  - They'll Never Keep Us Down - (Box 378)
    #282
- Railway Labor Executive Assoc. - Working on the Railroads (1962) - #1 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 379.1)
  - Railway Labor Executive Assoc. - Working on the Railroads (1962) - (Box 379)
    #1 (2 copies) // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Railway Labor Executive Assoc. - Working on the Railroads (1962) - #1 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 379.2)
- March on Washington - The Official Album -#2 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 380)
  - March on Washington - The Official Album - (Box 380)
    #2 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- The Original - Talking Union and other Union Songs - #4 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 381)
  - The Original - Talking Union and other Union Songs - (Box 381)
    #4 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Travis, Merle -- Songs of the Coal Mines -- #5 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 382)
  - Travis, Merle: Songs of the Coal Mines -- (Box 382)
    #5 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Hillstrom, Joseph 1879-1915 -- Songs of Joe Hill (pseudo) -- #6 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 383)
  - Hillstrom, Joseph 1879-1915: Songs of Joe Hill (pseudo) -- (Box 383)
    #6 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- 900 Miles and Other Railroad Songs - #7 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 384)
  - 900 Miles and Other Railroad Songs - (Box 384)
    #7 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Glazer, Joe - Textile Voices - Songs and Stories of the Mills - #8 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 385)
  - Glazer, Joe - Textile Voices - Songs and Stories of the Mills - (Box 385)
    #8 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- The Songs and Stories of Aunt Molly Jackson -- Songs told by Aunt Molly Jackson & Songs sung by John Greenway - #10 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 386)
  - The Songs and Stories of Aunt Molly Jackson: Songs told by Aunt Molly Jackson & Songs sung by John Greenway - (Box 386)
    #10 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Picket Line Songs -- Jefferson Chorus - #11 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 387)
  - Picket Line Songs: Jefferson Chorus - (Box 387)
    #11 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Songs for a Better Tomorrow #12 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 388)
  - Songs for a Better Tomorrow (Box 388)
    #12 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Vanderbilt, Amy -- The Do's and Don'ts When You Apply for a Job -- #14 (Box 389)
  - Vanderbilt, Amy: (Box 389)
    The Do's and Don'ts When You Apply for a Job -- #14
- McColl, Ewan -- British Industrial Folk Songs -- #15 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 390)
  - McColl, Ewan: British Industrial Folk Songs -- (Box 390)
    #15 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Glazer, Joe -- Down in the Coal Mine -- #16 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 391)
  - Glazer, Joe: Down in the Coal Mine -- (Box 391)
    #16 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Glazer, Joe -- Garbage -- #17 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 392)
  - Glazer, Joe: Garbage -- (Box 392)
    #17 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- King, Martin Luther, Jr. -- At 1199 -- #19 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 393)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: At 1199 -- (Box 393)
    #19 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Travis, Merle -- Back Home -- #20 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 394)
  - Travis, Merle: Back Home -- (Box 394)
    #20 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Sing a Labor Song -- Sung by Dick Wright and the Wright Trio -- #21 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 395)
  - Sing a Labor Song: Sung by Dick Wright and the Wright Trio -- (Box 395)
    #21 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Lang, Lucy (Fox) Robins -- Portrait of Samuel Gompers; AF of L Madge Smegoff Interviews, Lucy Robin Lang -- #22 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 396)
  - Lang, Lucy (Fox) Robins: Portrait of Samuel Gompers; AF of L Madge Smegoff Interviews, Lucy Robin Lang -- (Box 396)
    #22 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- The Magic Blackjack - International Union, United Automobile (1947) -- #23 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 397)
  - The Magic Blackjack - International Union, United Automobile (1947): (Box 397)
    #23 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Image of Freedom and 20 years of the CIO -- Narrator: Melvyn Douglas with Joe Glazer -- #26 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 398)
  - Image of Freedom and 20 years of the CIO: Narrator: Melvyn Douglas with Joe Glazer -- (Box 398)
    #26 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Congress of Industrial Organizations -- 8 New Songs of Labor by Joe Glazer -- #27 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 399)
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations: 8 New Songs of Labor by Joe Glazer -- (Box 399)
    #27 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Brotherhood of Railway Clerks -- Discussion of Union Shop Amendment to Railway Labor Act by Geo. M. Harrison -- #28 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 400)
  - Brotherhood of Railway Clerks: Discussion of Union Shop Amendment to Railway Labor Act by Geo. M. Harrison -- (Box 400)
    #28 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Brotherhood of Railway Clerks -- Discussion of Railway Labor's Polititcal League by Phil E. Zeigler -- #29 (Box 401)
  - Brotherhood of Railway Clerks: Discussion of Railway Labor's Political League by Phil E. Zeigler -- (Box 401)
    #29
- Excerpts from James C. Petrillo's testimony before Congressional Committee - Jan. 21, 1949 -- #30 (Box 402)
  - Excerpts from James C. Petrillo's testimony before Congressional Committee - Jan. 21, 1949: (Box 402)
    #30
- Glazer, Joe -- Joe McCarthy's Band and Give Away Boys; Labor Arts. Detroit, Michigan -- #32 (Box 403)
  - Glazer, Joe: Joe McCarthy's Band and Give Away Boys; Labor Arts. Detroit, Michigan -- (Box 403)
    #32
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Northeast Dept. -- My Name is Mary Brown -- #34 (Box 404)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Northeast Dept.: My Name is Mary Brown -- (Box 404)
    #34
- Congress of Industrial Organizations. Dept. of Education and Research -- A Promise Ain't A Promise Anymore; You Gotta Go Down -- Sung by Joe Glazer -- #35 (Box 405)
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations. Dept. of Education and Research: A Promise Ain't A Promise Anymore; You Gotta Go Down -- Sung by Joe Glazer -- (Box 405)
    #35
- Congress of Industrial Organization. Dept. of Education and Research -- Solidarity; Give Away Boys -- Sung by Joe Glazer & the PAC Bucks -- #36 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 406)
  - Congress of Industrial Organization. Dept. of Education and Research: Solidarity; Give Away Boys -- Sung by Joe Glazer & the PAC Bucks -- (Box 406)
    #36 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and gricultural Implement Workers of America. Education Dept. -- Midnight Vision - July 20, 1947 -- #39 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 407)
  - International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and agricultural Implement Workers of America. Education Dept.: Midnight Vision - July 20, 1947 -- (Box 407)
    #39 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Textile Workers Union of America. Education Dept. - The Story of Henderson - November 17, 1959 -- #41 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 408)
  - Textile Workers Union of America. Education Dept. - The Story of Henderson - November 17, 1959: (Box 408)
    #41 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Kansas City Fire and Marine Insurance Company -- Your Company's Record for 1948 -- #42 (Box 409)
  - Kansas City Fire and Marine Insurance Company: Your Company's Record for 1948 -- (Box 409)
    #42
- New York Cloak Joint Board, ILGWU -- We Work --We Sing! Local 91 -- #43 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 410)
  - New York Cloak Joint Board, ILGWU: We Work --We Sing! Local 91 -- (Box 410)
    #43 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Glazer, Joe -- Solidarity Forever; The Mill Was Made of Marble; Song of the Furniture Workers -- #44 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 411)
  - Glazer, Joe: Solidarity Forever; The Mill Was Made of Marble; Song of the Furniture Workers -- (Box 411)
    #44 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- AFL-CIO, Industrial Union Dept. -- Side 1: Panel Discussion, Union Shop: The Moral Issue; Side 2:Highlights of Address by John I. Snyder -- #45 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 412)
  - AFL-CIO, Industrial Union Dept.: Side 1: Panel Discussion, Union Shop: The Moral Issue; Side 2:Highlights of Address by John I. Snyder -- (Box 412)
    #45 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Michigan State Univ. - Labor and Industrial Relations Center -- Highlights -- #46 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 413)
  - Michigan State Univ. - Labor and Industrial Relations Center: Highlights -- (Box 413)
    #46 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Railway Labor Executives Assoc. -- The Railroad Worker and His Songs, Washington, DC 1959 -- Merrill Jay Singers -- #47 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 414)
  - Railway Labor Executives Assoc.: The Railroad Worker and His Songs, Washington, DC 1959 -- Merrill Jay Singers -- (Box 414)
    #47 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- General Telephone Co. of Michigan -- A Message for you (1964) -- #48 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 415)
  - General Telephone Co. of Michigan: A Message for you (1964) -- (Box 415)
    #48 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Union Oil Company of California -- The Facts Behind the Figures -- #49 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 416)
  - Union Oil Company of California: The Facts Behind the Figures -- (Box 416)
    #49 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Glazer, Joe. Union Train. - #51// non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 417)
  - Glazer, Joe. Union Train. - (Box 417)
    #51// non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- 1958 Vote Spots. Presto Recording Corp. Paramus, NJ. From Rubber Workers. - #53 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 418)
  - 1958 Vote Spots. Presto Recording Corp. Paramus, NJ. From Rubber Workers. - (Box 418)
    #53 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Glazer, Joe. The Song of the Guaranteed Wage, Weve Got a Plan, and I Like Ike. UAW Education Department. Washington, DC - #54 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 419)
  - Glazer, Joe. The Song of the Guaranteed Wage, Weve Got a Plan, and I Like Ike. UAW Education Department. Washington, DC - (Box 419)
    #54 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Canadian Labour Congress. A Century of Song. (Canadas album of labor songs). Ottawa - #68 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 420)
  - Canadian Labour Congress. A Century of Song. (Canadas album of labor songs). Ottawa - (Box 420)
    #68 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- United Sates Laws, Statutes, etc. Taft - Hartley Act. Enrichment Records, New York, New York. 1966. - #70 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 421)
  - United Sates Laws, Statutes, etc. Taft - Hartley Act. Enrichment Records, New York, New York. 1966. - (Box 421)
    #70 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Glazer, Joe. Songs of Coal. - #73 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 422)
  - Glazer, Joe. Songs of Coal. - (Box 422)
    #73 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Pfizer and Co., Inc. A message to our Pfizer associates throughout the world. - #74 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 423)
  - Pfizer and Co., Inc. A message to our Pfizer associates throughout the world. - (Box 423)
    #74 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- The Golden Spike Centennial Celebration Commission. Official Souvenir Album. - #76 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 424)
  - The Golden Spike Centennial Celebration Commission. Official Souvenir Album. - (Box 424)
    #76 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Wheeler, Billy Edd. Coal Tattoo - #77 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 425)
  - Wheeler, Billy Edd. Coal Tattoo - (Box 425)
    #77 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Movin On. United Transportation Union - #80 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 426)
  - Movin On. United Transportation Union - (Box 426)
    #80 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Dane, Barbara. I Hate the Capitalist System - #81 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 427)
  - Dane, Barbara. I Hate the Capitalist System - (Box 427)
    #81 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Original Huelga Songs. Sung by Dan and Judy Rose-Redwood. - #91 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 428)
  - Original Huelga Songs. Sung by Dan and Judy Rose-Redwood. - (Box 428)
    #91 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Movin On. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. - #91 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 429)
  - Movin On. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. - (Box 429)
- Glazer, Joe. Joe Glazer Sings Labor Songs. (Collector Records 1918) - #98 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 430)
  - Glazer, Joe. Joe Glazer Sings Labor Songs. (Collector Records 1918) - (Box 430)
    #98 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- The Human Condition with Beverly Grant. - #99 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 431)
  - The Human Condition with Beverly Grant. - (Box 431)
    #99 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- International Woodworkers of America. Joe Glazer Sings Songs for Woodworkers. - #105 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 432)
  - International Woodworkers of America. Joe Glazer Sings Songs for Woodworkers. - (Box 432)
    #105 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Steady As She Goes. Songs and chanteys from the days of commercial sail. - #106 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 433)
  - Steady As She Goes. Songs and chanteys from the days of commercial sail. - (Box 433)
    #106 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Glazer, Joe. Songs of the Wobblies. I Will Win. - #107 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 434)
  - Steady As She Goes. Songs and chanteys from the days of commercial sail. - (Box 434)
- Songs of Steel and Struggle. The Story of the Steelworkers. Sung by Joe Glazer. - #108 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 435)
  - Songs of Steel and Struggle. The Story of the Steelworkers. Sung by Joe Glazer. - (Box 435)
    #108 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Church, Sam. Black Gold. - #109 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 436)
  - Church, Sam. Black Gold. - (Box 436)
    #109 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Uehlein, Joe. Groundwork. Songs of Working People. - #117 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 437)
  - Uehlein, Joe. Groundwork. Songs of Working People. - (Box 437)
    #117 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Penn, Larry. Workin For a Living. Songs by Larry Penn. - #118 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 438)
  - Penn, Larry. Workin For a Living. Songs by Larry Penn. - (Box 438)
    #118 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Killen, Louis. Gallant Lads are We - Songs of the British Industrial Revolution. - 119 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 439)
  - Killen, Louis. Gallant Lads are We - Songs of the British Industrial Revolution. - (Box 439)
    #119 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Seeger, Mike. Tipple, Loom, and Rail. Songs of the Industrialization of the South. - #120 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 440)
  - Seeger, Mike. Tipple, Loom, and Rail. Songs of the Industrialization of the South. - (Box 440)
    #120 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. This Land is Your Land, Songs of Social Justice. - #121 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 441)
  - International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. This Land is Your Land, Songs of Social Justice. - (Box 441)
    #121 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Talking Union. Dedicated to the Memory of Joe Hill. The Almanac Singers, Keynote Recordings. Album No. 106 - #122 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 442)
  - Talking Union. Dedicated to the Memory of Joe Hill. The Almanac Singers, Keynote Recordings. Album No. 106 - (Box 442)
    #122 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Glazer, Joe. Eight New Songs for Labor. - #123 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 443)
  - Glazer, Joe. Eight New Songs for Labor. - (Box 443)
    #123 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Berkeley, Roy. Songs from the FDR Years. With Tim Woodbridge. Berkeley Longview records. - #124 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 444)
  - Berkeley, Roy. Songs from the FDR Years. With Tim Woodbridge. Berkeley Longview records. - (Box 444)
    #124 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Juravich, Tom. Trying to Break My Union. UAW Local 430. 1981. - #125 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 445)
  - Juravich, Tom. Trying to Break My Union. UAW Local 430. 1981. - quested (Box 445)
    #125 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Coalition of Labor Union Women. "Bread and Raises, Songs for Working Women." - #126 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 446.1)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women. Bread and Raises, Songs for Working Women. - (Box 446)
    #126 (2 copies) // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Coalition of Labor Union Women. "Bread and Raises, Songs for Working Women." - #126 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 446.2)
- Image of History; Twenty Years of the CIO. Narrator: Melvyn Douglas. - #127 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 447)
  - Image of History; Twenty Years of the CIO. Narrator: Melvyn Douglas. - (Box 447)
    #127 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Solidarity Day. Worker Records - #128 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 448)
  - Solidarity Day. Worker Records - (Box 448)
    #128 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Glazer, Joe. "Jellybean Blues, Songs of Reaganomics." (Collector Records) v.1 - #129 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 449.1)
  - Glazer, Joe. Jellybean Blues, Songs of Reaganomics. (Collector Records) v.1 - (Box 449)
    #129 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Glazer, Joe. "Jellybean Blues, Songs of Reaganomics." (Collector Records) v.1 - #129 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 449.2)
- Free Labor Sings. 3 records in one album, with booklet. Gift of Wm. Freedland - #71 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 450)
  - Free Labor Sings. 3 records in one album, with booklet. Gift of Wm. Freedland - (Box 450)
    #71 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested
- Debs, Eugene V. Eugene V. Debs - Trade Unionist, Socialist, Revolutionary, 1855-1926 - #110 // non-circ. / make a loan copy if requested (Box 451)
  - Debs, Eugene V. Eugene V. Debs - Trade Unionist, Socialist, Revolutionary, 1855-1926 - (Box 451)